(Howard(off):)Hey, Mike.
(Howard(off):)Let me help you out, there.
(Howard:)Thanks.
What's wrong with your mom?
(Howard:)Oh, her gout's flaring up.
(Howard:)Turns out an apple pie a day
docs not keep the doctor away.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)How can
one little toe hurt so bad?
(Howard:)Maybe because that little piggy
is being crushed by the barn!
(Howard:)She should quiet down soon.
(Howard:)I gave her enough pain meds
to choke a... well, her.
I guess we're going to
have to do all the cooking.
(Howard:)I have a better idea.
(Bernadette:)If you think you're
going to make me
(Bernadette:)do all this by myself,
you're crazy.
I was going to make Raj
do it all by himself.
(Bernadette:)Oh, well, that's a great idea.
(Amy:)No traffic, we're sailing.
(Sheldon:)Yes. Like we're on a ship.
(Sheldon:)Coming from Africa to America.
(Amy:)Sheldon, that's
completely inappropriate.
(Amy:)You can't keep comparing
yourself to a slave.
(Sheldon:)Yes, Miss Amy.